<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Popular Movies - Stage 1</string>

    <string name="sort_by">Sort by...</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="sort_key">sort</string>
    <string name="sort_default">popularity.desc</string>
    <string name="no_overview">No overview found</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="unfavorite">Unfavorite</string>
    <string name="trailers">Trailers:</string>
    <string name="reviews">Reviews:</string>
    <string name="dummy_review">When one thinks of a typical super-hero actioner, they imagine the boisterous boundaries that are associated with such an explosive genre: eye-popping special effects, outlandish and grand-standing villains, world domination escapades, complex yet flashy super-heroes that seem unreal and unapologetic and a big scale of unbelievable escapism that is tellingly becoming of a comic book epic on the big screen for the hungry eyes of the giddy moviegoer. Remember, all these described elements are not a bad thing when it comes to larger than life comic book/superhero fantasies. In fact, we almost insist that our volt-minded vehicles have some kinetic kick to its pulsating, pithy adventures. After all, there is certainly nothing wrong with that approach to the cinematic sensationalism of summertime popcorn pleasers and the costumed heroes that take us on that daring, rollicking ride of magical mayhem.\\r\\n\\r\\nHowever, director Peyton Reed’s ‘Ant-Man’ symbolizes a different texture and tone to the familiar action-packed world of Marvel Comics’ outrageous universe both on the printed pages and in the dark movie theaters. It does not necessarily use the overwrought or ultra-stimulating tactics to sell its percolating product as a super-charged heroic fable of mighty manipulators out to save the planet in the tradition of frantic favorites such as ‘The Avengers’ film franchise for instance. Instead, ‘Ant-Man’ relies on its small and intimate take of quirkiness, introspection, a gentle doomsday message of despair and a measurement of an awkward man that wears his bugged-out wardrobe with a sense of curiosity and conviction. In essence, ‘Ant-Man’ is a costumed caper that is high-spirited in its low-key excitement…</string>
    <string name="favorites_pref">favorites_pref</string>
    <string name="favorites">favorites</string>


</resources>
